[Uvogin] You tell the boss…
I’m not leaving.
I can’t go back
until I settle the score
with that damn chain user!
[theme song playing]
CHASING x AND x WAITING
[narrator] Hisoka,
who joined the Phantom Troupe,
for a chance to fight the leader, Chrollo,
has proposed a partnership with Kurapika,
who is seeking revenge on the group.
[Hisoka] What are you going to do?
Will you work with me?
Or would you rather…
fight alone?
[phone ringing]
Go ahead.
Yes, it’s me.
[Melody] Terrible news.
The big man we captured has escaped.
Escaped? All on his own?
[Melody] No.
Some Phantom Troupe members
disguised themselves as Mafia henchmen
and came for him.
[Kurapika] And our leader?
Not sure.
We haven’t been able to reach him.
[gasps]
[Melody] We’re moving to plan B.
Get back here as soon as possible.
Understood.
[Kurapika] Hisoka,
I have a question for you.
Where can I find the Scarlet Eyes?
[Hisoka] Unfortunately,
that happened before I joined.
The Boss sells every item
after reveling in the spoils for a bit.
I assume the Scarlet Eyes
were no exception.
And that’s all
I can tell you on the matter.
But keep this in mind:
A spider will keep going
until you crush its head.
I suggested we form an alliance,
but not that we fight side by side.
Merely the give and take
of certain information.
And if it ceases to benefit us,
there is no further obligation
to cooperate.
Simple enough?
What do you say?
[Kurapika] I’ll be back here
at the same time tomorrow.
So? What do we do now?
Our leader’s probably dead already.
And we still
haven’t completed the mission…
We should report this to the boss,
don’t you think?
That little girl is our boss in name only.
[Squala] Yeah, it was somebody else
who hired us.
Light Nostrade.
Her father.
Our orders come directly from him.
The leader just relayed them to us.
And he was the only one
who knew how to contact him.
We have no choice.
We have to report this to the boss.
Boss... Boss.
[stirring groan]
[Neon] Hold on, what time is it?
[Kurapika] It’s two in the morning.
[gasps in shock]
Oh, no! What about the auction?!
[Kurapika] It's been called off.
Huh?
Completely? Why? What for?
There was a gang of thieves
who attacked the auction hall.
Huh?
[Kurapika] Baise, Ivlenkov, and Tocino
lost their lives in the incident.
Huh?
[Squala] We can’t reach the leader,
so he might also be…
No way…
But what about the mummy?
Was it really stolen?
I wanted it so much…
-[Kurapika exhales]
-[Squala grunts]
Seems the Mafia moved the merchandise
to a safe location.
[light giggle] That's great!
When’s the next one?
There’s another auction soon, right?
[Kurapika] We don't know yet.
You don’t? But why not?
In any case,
the leader handled all communication
with your father.
So, I’m afraid we don’t know anything.
And we can’t act
until we’ve received his orders.
[Neon] Don’t ask me. I have no idea.
But here, just ask daddy.
I’ve got his number
saved here in my phone.
Squala. You make the call.
[gasps] Why do I have to?
You’re the most experienced
and we need a new leader.
-So, it should be you
-Oh no!
That’s completely out of the question!
I’m just not leader material.
Then perhaps we should put it
to a vote to be fair.
We need to make the call
as soon as possible.
And my vote’s for Kurapika.
He’s the one who captured the bandit,
and he’s shown excellent judgment.
I believe he would make
the most effective leader.
Works for me.
I vote for Kurapika, too.
That’s that.
So, you make the call.
Very well.
Then as interim leader,
I’ll call Mr. Nostrade.
But only...
until we can confirm
what’s really become of Dalzollene.
Further choices will be made
by Mr. Nostrade.
I didn’t expect this to happen so soon…
It would be inappropriate for me to call.
So, would you please
provide an introduction?
Okay.
[Neon] Here. I’m putting him on now.
[Kurapika] Hello?
Is it true that Dalzollene
has been killed?
[Kurapika] Yes, sir.
That’s quite hard to believe.
He is a Nen user.
He’s trained to withstand ten gunshots
without sustaining any injuries.
He was killed by outlaws
known as the Phantom Troupe.
Wait… The Spiders?
[Kurapika] I had the opportunity
to see them in action.
One of them stopped a bazooka round
with his bare hand.
My name is Kurapika
and I’m the interim leader.
Can you please tell me
how you would like us to proceed?
Of course.
But first I want to hear what you think.
[Kurapika] I believe your daughter
should leave
Yorknew City immediately, sir.
I’m not confident that we can protect her
in the event of unforeseen circumstances.
[Nostrade] I agree with your assessment,
but my daughter has a say, as well.
I want to respect her wishes
whenever possible.
Her safety’s my top priority.
Hmm...
Understood.
I’m on my way there right now,
so I should arrive
sometime tomorrow evening.
I promise I’ll do my best
to persuade Neon.
You will be the new leader, Kurapika.
Here is your first order:
Keep an eye on Neon until I get there.
Yes, sir. I will.
Your father wants you to know
he’ll be here tomorrow evening.
Really? That’s perfect!
When he lands,
I’ll get him to take me shopping!
Until then he made it quite clear
that he’d like you to stay in your room.
Aw...
I wanted to see the casino…
You stay here with the boss.
What?! Yeah, I got it.
I’ll be downstairs.
[gulping]
[refreshed exhale]
This is it!
It says here
that a dummy corporation
for the Nostrade family
owns that building you were in.
All right then, do you think
you can track down a list
of all the buildings
in this area the Nostrade family own?
Sure can!
I can also see,
if anyone has checked into a hotel
using the Nostrade name lately.
[metal bang]
Okay. I brought some more beer.
Hey! Thanks a lot!
Here ya go.
Know what you need, Uvo?
A Hunter’s License.
As long as you have the money,
you can dig up
all kinds of information from their site.
Unlike you guys,
I don’t like the idea of money.
If I want something, I take it.
[Shalnark] Well said!
-You’re an exemplary bandit.
-[Uvogin gulping]
Here.
They own two other buildings
in Yorknew City.
And there are three hotels
where members are staying.
All right.
This search shouldn’t take too long.
There.
Thanks, buddy.
I owe ya one.
[loud smooch]
Whoa! What are you doing?!
[chuckles] Well... I’m off.
[Franklin] What about the beer?
You guys can finish it.
Make sure you dispose of the body.
And try to make it quick.
Yeah.
-Later.
-Hey, Uvo!
Huh?
Don’t get careless out there.
No prob.
Family members…
Sounds like a good place to start.
[Kurapika] Look at this.
What’s that?
A list of the buildings the Nostrades own?
And a list of family members.
I didn’t know this was out there.
This website can only be accessed
by pro Hunters.
With this information,
they can find the location of this room
without any trouble at all.
There’s a website just for pro Hunters?
That means if one of our enemies
is a pro Hunter, too.
We’re in trouble.
We need to move the boss
to a different room right away.
[Melody] We do? In the same hotel?
It’s faster and cleaner that way.
But do not use aliases!
We’ll have Melody or Basho book the room.
And don’t let anyone leave,
especially the boss.
You got it.
[Kurapika]
Don’t check out of this one, either.
Hold on. What about you?
[Kurapika] I'll stay here.
Oh?!
Kurapika… You’re not thinking of...?
[man] I-- I don’t think
he’s a family member.
He’s a bodyguard for the boss’s daughter.
[Uvogin] His daughter?
Yeah.
She’s a freak who gets her kicks
out of collecting body parts.
[grunts] Eyeballs, organs, guts…
Oh! And she’s a fortune teller!
She’s really accurate, too!
That so?
Yeah! She’s got a long list
of clients in the Mafia.
Some of the community elders
practically worship her!
[nervous chuckle]
[Uvogin] Oh?
I mean it makes sense.
Our boss used his daughter’s power
to make his entire fortune.
Look, cut me some slack, all right?
I told you everything I know,
so just let me--
[Uvogin] Someone who can see the future.
So, she knew this attack was gonna happen?
The boss was right.
There weren’t any traitors among us
after all.
[Leorio] As it stands, we have a diamond
worth three million jenny
and 2.4 million in leftover cash.
Not to mention the 2.75
we made arm wrestling.
All told that’s
a total of around eight million.
We need at least nine billion.
That’s the minimum opening bid
for Greed Island,
so if we don’t have that,
there’s really no point.
But I don’t see how we’re gonna get there.
Not through legitimate channels anyway.
Yeah, I wouldn’t call
that kind of arm wrestling "legitimate."
All of the challengers toward the end
were a bunch of desperate losers
looking for revenge.
And that’s okay.
See, that was my goal
from the very beginning.
[Gon and Killua] Huh?
[Leorio] The more exaggerated the rumors,
the better.
What do you mean by that?
The arm wrestling was just bait.
[Gon] It was?
That is what’s gonna draw all the moles
out of hiding!
Wait, moles?
I don’t think I get it.
Why do we want moles?
[Leorio] Okay, take it easy.
Just let me explain…
[Gon and Killua] [uncertain grunt]
[Leorio] Step right up!
Conditional auction!
We’ve got a diamond sitting here
that’s worth three million jenny!
Arm wrestling decides the winner!
The first person to beat this boy
wins the diamond.
The entry fee’s 10,000 jenny.
What? He’s just a kid!
I just might try it…
Don't bother.
That kid beat 500 people yesterday,
no problem.
[man] Really?
Yeah, really, and more than 20 of ‘em
got their arms broken.
Seriously?
[Leorio] [chuckles] The rumors
are starting to spread nicely.
Well, in that case…
Outta my way.
Oh! Do we have our first challenger?
[short man] Not quite.
[gasps]
[short man]
I already know my man can’t beat your kid.
I was watching yesterday.
[Leorio] Then what do you want?
You interested in makin’ some real money?
What do you mean?
I know where you can make serious cash.
Not the measly pocket change
you’re pulling here.
You can make hundreds...
no, thousands of times more, easy.
[chuckling]
So, are these two the moles?
Yeah. It looks like
we just landed a big fish!
Fish? So... they’re not moles?
Will you please stop talking?
It doesn’t matter!
[short man] Here we are.
[elevator dings]
[straining]
[grunting]
[cheering]
[Killua] Oh, wow.
I can feel the bloodlust.
This competition accepts all comers,
and it really pays out.
The spectators bet on each match
and the winner gets ten percent
of all bets placed.
We’re talking billions
wagered on each match.
But that means every single win
could make you millions!
More if you play your cards right.
I get a commission
but it’s only 50 percent
of whatever you earn.
Fifty? Isn’t that a bit steep?
If I don’t enter your name,
you can’t participate.
Besides you can bet your own money.
That kid’ll get great odds,
so you’ll make it back
a hundred times over.
Okay, I’m sold!
We’re in! Gon! Do it!
Huh?
[referee]
Well? Do we have any other challengers?
[short man] Right over here!
This kid thinks he’s got what it takes.
All right!
[gasping]
Sorry to disappoint you, folks!
But the arm wrestling
has officially been canceled!
Instead, we’re gonna do
a little bit of conditional auctioning!
[upset crowd]
What’s wrong? Why’s it canceled?
I, uh... I don’t actually know…
And all you have to do to win is...
play a game of hide-and-seek!
Hide-and-seek? Really?
[punk] We’ll start by passing out flyers!
Now take a good look
at those pictures, folks!
Don’t forget ‘em,
because the seven guys and gals you see
are your targets!
Hey… I’ve seen that girl with the glasses.
Me too. She arm-wrestled me.
[man] Wait…
You think they’re the ones responsible
for what happened last night?
Yeah. You mean the attack
on the auction, right?
[gasps]
[punk] In order to win the bid,
all you have to do is capture a target
and deliver them to us.
For each, you’ll walk away
with the tidy sum of…
wait for it… two billion jenny!
[crowd gasping]
[punk] There is no time limit.
And it doesn’t matter
if they’re dead or alive!
Interested? Then catch one and call us!
Two billion each is a lot!
And if we catch all seven,
that’s 14 billion!
[punk] All it costs to participate
is a mere five million jenny!
We’re participating, right?
[Gon] Sure…
[participant 1] That’s right.
I’ll fax you the information.
[participant 2] Check the website.
We’ll pay for anything concrete.
[Leorio] We’re gonna need to hurry.
[Killua] No rush.
They won’t be able to catch our targets.
[Leorio and Gon] Huh?
Even the Mafia’s having
a hard time with them.
What do you mean?
The "conditional auction"
they’re having?
It’s nothing more than a big bounty hunt.
It’s like...
the Mafia’s admitting
they can’t catch these targets.
Or not alone, anyway.
You’ve got a point there.
They were willing to put
everything else on hold
just so they could track them down...
I heard, last night, someone
attacked the underground auction.
But who would do that?!
Unless… maybe it was them.
You think that’s the reason
they’ve got a bounty on their heads?
Yup.
And if they stole from the Mafia,
they’ve got a screw loose.
But think.
Who do we know
that’s crazy enough to do that?
The Phantom Troupe!
Now that you mention it,
what’s Kurapika been up to?
Dunno. He should be here
in the city by now
but he hasn’t called yet.
Then I’ll call him.
[phone rings]
[phone continues ringing]
He's not answering.
Maybe he’s working…
Working?
Yeah, I heard he picked up a job
as a bodyguard a while back.
I bet it’s some big shot VIP.
He’s looking for the Scarlet Eyes,
so probably someone in the underworld.
What if he was guarding them
at the auction hall
and then got caught up in the attack?
He wouldn’t have let
something like that happen.
If the Troupe attacked,
Kurapika would be tracking them down
even as we speak.
I wouldn’t be surprised,
if he’s captured a few of ‘em already.
I hope you're right.
[ringing tone]
[phone ringing]
[clatter]
You by yourself?
That’s pretty impressive.
Where do you want to die?
I’ll let you decide the location.
I’d prefer somewhere remote,
so we won’t be a nuisance.
I don’t want your screams
to bother anyone.
[angry grunt]
[narrator] Uvogin has come
to get revenge for his capture
and restore his wounded pride.
And Kurapika has long awaited the chance
to exact revenge upon the Phantom Troupe.
Their battle is about to begin.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is our Hunterpedia!
Today, we're introducing Squala,
one of Neon’s guards.
A Manipulator who controls dogs
using his Nen.
And he’s actually dating Neon’s maid,
Miss Eliza.
-Meow, meow!
-Woof, woof!
[Gon] Next time:
"Condition x and x Condition."
Explain the difference
using 30 words or less!
[Killua] A condition is a rule,
and a condition’s a covenant
with yourself!